atlas-sys.com 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy — Atlas Systems, Inc.

## **Privacy Statement**

This privacy statement explains how Atlas Systems (also referred to as “we,” “us,” and “our”) uses any personal information we collect from or about you, through our interactions with you, and through our products and services, including this website. 

 **What information do we collect about you?  **

We collect information about you to effectively operate our website and provide information to you about our products and services. We may also collect personal information when you voluntarily submit it to us, like through a website “contact us” form or email for sales or support information. We collect payment information that you provide us in order to pay for and use our products and services. 

 **How will we use the information about you?  **

We may use your personal information to manage our relationship with you. We collect information about you to process and manage orders. We may use your information for marketing purposes, and we may retain your information in order to protect our legal rights. 

 **Marketing**

We may use your personal information to communicate with your and to personalize our communications with you. We may email you information we think may be of interest to you. We do not rent or sell personal information or emails lists to third parties, but we may work with a third-party to help market our products and services. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please contact: sales@atlas-sys.com. 

 **Social media plug-ins**

Our website features four plug-ins for easy sharing and following our social media pages: Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, and Instagram. Being on our website does not automatically result in sharing data on these social media networks. These plugins remain inactive (idle) until clicked upon. Once clicked upon, you will be taken to the social media site, with their own privacy statements (which you are recommended to read). 

 **Information security**

We care about and are committed to the security of your personal data. When we collect information about you, we also make sure that your information is protected from unauthorized access, loss, manipulation, falsification, destruction or unauthorized disclosure. This is done through appropriate technical measures. We delete all information deemed no longer necessary. 

 **International (cross-border) transfers of personal data**

Atlas Systems is a US based company that operates globally. Accordingly, cross border sharing of your personal data may be essential to our operations. Where we transfer store, and process your personal information outside of the EU, we have ensured that appropriate safeguards are in place to ensure an adequate level of data protection. 

 **Access to your information**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would to review, correct or remove some or all of your personal data from our systems, please email privacy@atlas-sys.com or write to us at the address below. We will provide you with a copy of the data. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. We will fulfil your request by sending your copy electronically, unless the request expressly specifies a different method. We reserve the right to charge an administrative fee for additional requests. 

 **Cookies & similar technologies **

We use cookies (small text files placed on your computer or device to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information). This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. You can set your browser not to accept cookies. Your browser may also have the ability to block tracking. 

 **Retention of personal data**

We retain personal information for as long as necessary to provide the products and services you have requested, or for other essential purposes such as complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing agreements. 

 **Other websites**

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy statement only applies to this website. 

 **Disclosure of information to third parties**

We may provide your information to third parties who handle information on our behalf. This may help us respond to your inquiry, manage our relationship with you, and to comply with legal, regulatory, or national security obligations. We do not rent or sell personal information to third parties. By providing personal information through our website, you are consenting to these disclosures. 

 **Atlas server hosting services (“SHS”)  **

If you are a customer of Atlas or a patron of one of our customers, you may utilize our SHS. 

The above policy does not apply to our security and privacy practices in connection with your access to and use of the SHS. These security and privacy practices, including how we protect, collect, and use electronic data, communications or other materials entered by the Subscriber, Permitted Users, Patrons and others through Subscriber into the Software which is stored by the SHS (“Subscriber Data”), are detailed in and governed by our End User Software Agreement, or such other applicable agreement between you and Atlas Systems relating to your access to and use of such Services (collectively referred to as the “Software Agreement”). 

We collect information under the direction of our Subscribers, and have no direct relationship with individuals whose personal information we process in connection with our Subscriber’s use of our Services. Further, per our End User Software Agreement all data remains the exclusive property of our Subscriber. If you are an individual who interacts with a Subscriber using our Services (such as a customer of one of our Subscribers) and would either like to amend your contact information or no longer wish to be contacted by one of our Subscribers that use our Services, please contact the Subscriber that you interact with directly. 

Subscribers to our Services are solely responsible for establishing policies for and ensuring compliance with all applicable laws and regulations, as well as any and all privacy policies, agreements or other obligations, relating to the collection of personal information in connection with the use of our Services and Software by individuals (also referred to as “subscriber data”) with whom our Subscribers interact. If you are an individual who interacts with a Subscriber using our Services, then you will be directed to contact our Subscriber for assistance with any requests or questions relating to your personal information. 

We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our Services. Transfers to subsequent third parties for these purposes are governed by the Software Agreements with our Subscribers. 

 **Children’s privacy**

We do not intentionally collect information on anyone under the age of 13. 

 **Changes to our privacy statement**

We keep our privacy statement under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. 

This privacy statement was last updated on May 29, 2018. 

 **How to contact us**

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy statement or information we hold about you. 

By mail: 

Atlas Systems  
5712 Cleveland Street Suite 200  
Virginia Beach, VA 23462  
ATTN: Privacy Manager

By email:  [privacy@atlas-sys.com](mailto:privacy@atlas-sys.com)
